Guide to the Northern Pacific Railway Company Records 1870-1968
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Engineering Department, 1870-1968; Subgroup 1; 165.25 linear feet and 14 oversize volumes
  - Main Line General, 1870-1965; Series I; 22 linear feet and 3 oversize volumes
    - Sunnyside (Washington) Station, 1904-1907 and undated; Subseries 7; 4.5 linear feet
      - Construction Correspondence, 1906-03 (Box-folder 26/4)
      - Construction Correspondence, 1905-04 (Box-folder 26/5)
      - Construction Correspondence, 1906-05 (Box-folder 27/1)
      - Construction Correspondence, 1906-06 (Box-folder 27/2)
      - Construction Correspondence, 1906-07 - 1906-08 (Box-folder 27/3)
      - Construction Correspondence, 1906-09 - 1907-08 (Box-folder 27/4)
      - Pipe and Box Culverts, 1905-07 - 1905-12, 1906-01, and 1907-03 (Box-folder 27/5)
      - Travel Passes Correspondence, 1905-08 - 1906-09 (Box-folder 27/6)
      - Payroll, 1905-09 - 1906-09 (Box-folder 28/1)
      - Estimates of Work, 1905-08 - 1906-09 (Box-folder 28/2)
      - Return of Time, 1905-08 - 1906-10 (Box-folder 28/3)
      - Estimates of Work, 1905-06 - 1905-10 (Box-folder 28/4)
      - Estimates of Work, 1905-11 - 1906-03 (Box-folder 28/5)
      - Estimates of Work, 1906-03 - 1906-10 (Box-folder 28/6)
      - Force Reports, 1905-08 - 1905-12 (Box-folder 29A/1)
      - Force Reports, 1906-01 - 1906-09 (Box-folder 29A/2)
      - Force Account Reports, 1906-06 - 1906-09 (Box-folder 29A/3)
      - Expense Reports, 1905-05 - 1906-10 (Box-folder 29A/4)
      - Reports of Instruments 1905-03 - 1906-12 (Box-folder 29A/5)
      - Work Train, 1906-01 - 1906-04 and 1906-08 (Box-folder 29A/6)
      - Construction Progress Reports, 1905-07 - 1906-09 (Box-folder 29A/7)
      - Report of Work, 1905-04 - 1905-12 (Box-folder 29A/8)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1905-04 - 1905-07 (Box-volume 29B/43B)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1905-08 - 1905-11 (Box-volume 29B/43C)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1905-11 - 1906-04 (Box-volume 29B/43D)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1906-04 - 1906-10 (Box-volume 29B/43E)
      - Material Inventory Book, undated (Box-volume 29B/43F)
      - Outgoing Correspondence: L.S. Oakes, 1905-06 - 1905-08 (Box-volume 29C/43G)
      - Outgoing Correspondence: L.S. Oakes, 1905-08 - 1906-05 (Box-volume 29C/43H)
      - Outgoing Correspondence: L.S. Oakes, 1905-08 - 1905-10 (Box-volume 29C/43I)
      - Outgoing Correspondence: L.S. Oakes, 1905-10 - 1905-12 (Box-volume 29C/43J)
      - Outgoing Correspondence: L.S. Oakes, 1905-12 - 1906-01 (Box-volume 29C/43K)
      - Outgoing Correspondence: L.S. Oakes, 1906-01 - 1906-02 (Box-volume 29C/43L)
      - Outgoing Correspondence: L.S. Oakes, 1906-02 - 1906-03 (Box-volume 29C/43M)
      - Outgoing Correspondence: L.S. Oakes, 1906-03 - 1906-06 (Box-volume 29C/43N)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, G.W. Lancaster, 1906-05 - 1906-08 (Box-volume 29C/43O)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, G.W. Lancaster, 1906-08 - 1906-09 (Box-volume 29C/43P)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, H.M. Stoudt and C.J. Waddell, 1906-11 - 1906-12 (Box-volume 29C/43Q)
    - Trout Creek/Belknap (Montana) Relocation, 1907-1909; Subseries 8; 0.5 linear feet
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1907-03 - 1907-06 (Box-volume 30/44)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1907-04 - 1908-09 (Box-volume 30/45)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1907-05 - 1908-05 (Box-volume 30/46)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1907-06 - 1907-08 (Box-volume 30/47)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1907-08 - 1908-12 (Box-volume 30/48)
      - Outgoing Correspondence, 1907-08 - 1909-01 (Box-volume 30/49)
    - White Pine Hill/Trout Creek (Montana) Grade Revision, 1907-1910; Subseries 9; 3.5 linear feet
      - Work Train Correspondence, 1907-05 - 1909-05 (Box-folder 31/1)
      - Monthly Instrument Reports, 1907-02 - 1909-03 (Box-folder 31/2)
      - Estimates of Original Cost and Northern Pacific Beneficial Association Elections, 1907-01 - 1907-06 (Box-folder 31/3)
      - Accounting Reports, 1907-07 - 1908-03 (Box-folder 31/4)
      - Accounting Reports, 1908-04 - 1908-08 (Box-folder 31/5)
      - Accounting Reports, 1908-09 - 1909-02 (Box-folder 31/6)
      - Accounting Reports, 1909-03 - 1909-05 (Box-folder 31/7)
      - Accounting Reports, 1909-06 - 1910-02 and 1910-12 (Box-folder 32/1)
      - Coal and Spurs Furnished to Contractors, 1907-05 - 1909-02 (Box-folder 32/2)
      - Releasing Cars, 1907-07 - 1908-12 (Box-folder 32/3)
      - Concrete Work, 1907-05 - 1908-05 (Box-folder 32/4)
      - Weekly Reports by Resident Engineers, 1907-06 - 1909-01 (Box-folder 32/5)
      - Weekly Reports of Chief Engineer, 1907-04 and 1907-08 - 1909-04 (Box-folder 32/6)
      - Main Line, 1907-05 - 1908-10 (Box-folder 32/7)
      - Delays, 1908-07 - 1908-10 (Box-folder 32/8)
      - Line Changes, 1907-03 - 1907-10 (Box-folder 32/9)
      - Crossings, County Roads, and Telegraphs, 1907-05 - 1908-11 (Box-folder 32/10)
      - Track Laying, 1907-07 - 1907-09 and 1908-05 - 1908-07 (Box-folder 33/1)
      - Track Laying, 1908-04 - 1908-08 and 1910-12 (Box-folder 33/2)
      - Reports of Track Laid - Heron, Trout Creek, and Belknap, Montana, 1908-06 - 1908-11 (Box-folder 33/3)
      - Bridges, Kelly Atkinson Contract, 1908-05 - 1909-01 (Box-folder 33/4)
      - Bridges and Culverts, 1907-05 - 1910-01 (Box-folder 33/5)
      - Material Requests, 1907-04 - 1907-12 (Box-folder 33/6)
      - Material Requests, 1908-01 - 1908-07 (Box-folder 34/1)
      - Material Requests, 1908-08 - 1909-04 and 1910-12 (Box-folder 34/2)
      - General Correspondence, 1907-03 - 1907-11 (Box-folder 34/3)
      - General Correspondence, 1907-12 - 1908-08 (Box-folder 34/4)
      - General Correspondence, 1908-09 - 1908-12 (Box-folder 34/5)
      - General Correspondence, 1909-01 - 1910-02 (Box-folder 34/6)
      - Expense Reports, 1907-03 - 1909-01 and 1910-01 - 1910-12 (Box-folder 34/7)
      - Monthly Estimates of Work, 1908-08 - 1909-11 (Box-folder 35/1)
      - Coaling and Water Supply, 1908-05 - 1909-05 (Box-folder 35/2)
      - Travel Passes, 1907-03 - 1907-09 (Box-folder 35/3)
      - Travel Passes, 1907-10 - 1908-03 (Box-folder 35/4)
      - Travel Passes, 1908-04 - 1909-05 (Box-folder 35/5)
      - Rights of Way, 1907-05 - 1907-10 and 1908-04 - 1910-04 (Box-folder 35/6)
      - Progress Reports, 1907-05 - 1909-04 (Box-folder 35/7)
      - Payroll, 1907-02 - 1907-11 and 1908-06 - 1909-11 (Box-folder 35/8)
      - Applications, 1907-02 - 1908-07 (Box-folder 35/9)
      - Requisitions, 1907-04 -1909-01 (Box-folder 35/10)
      - Accident Reports, 1907-07 - 1908-10 (Box-folder 35/11)
      - Construction Department Bills, 1907-07 - 1909-02 (Box-folder 36/1)
      - Expenses for Porter Brothers and Welch, 1908-06 - 1909-02 (Box-folder 36/2)
      - Operating Expenses, 1907-01 - 1909-03 (Box-folder 36/3)
      - Force Reports, All Residencies, 1907-05 - 1909-04 (Box-folder 36/4)
      - Force Reports, 1st Residency, 1907-05 - 1908-05 and 1908-09 - 1908-10 (Box-folder 36/5)
      - Force Reports, 2nd Residency, 1907-05 - 1909-01 (Box-folder 36/6)
      - Force Reports, 3rd Residency, 1907-05 - 1909-01 (Box-folder 36/7)
      - Force Reports, Porter Brothers and Welch, 1908-08-20 - 1908-11-14 (Box-folder 36/8)
      - Force Account Reports, All Residencies, 1908-07 - 1909-01 (Box-folder 36/9)
      - Force Account Reports, All Residencies, 1907-12 - 1909-03 (Box-folder 36/10)
      - Force Account Reports, 1st Residency, 1907-06 - 1908-05 (Box-folder 36/11)
      - Force Account Reports, 2nd Residency, 1907-06 - 1908-09 (Box-folder 36/12)
      - Force Account Reports, 3rd Residency, 1907-06 - 1908-07 (Box-folder 37/1)
      - Monthly Estimates of Work, 1907-06 - 1907-11 (Box-folder 37/2)
      - Monthly Estimates of Work, 1907-12 - 1908-05 (Box-folder 37/3)
      - Monthly Estimates of Work, 1908-06 - 1908-08 (Box-folder 37/4)
      - Monthly Estimates of Work, 1908-09 - 1908-11 (Box-folder 37/5)
      - Monthly Estimates of Work, 1908-12 - 1909-11 (Box-folder 37/6)
      - Monthly Inventory of Instruments, 1907-03 - 1908-08 and 1909-01 (Box-folder 37/7)
      - Work Train, 1909-01 - 1909-03 (Box-folder 37/8)
  - Second Main Line, 1905-1956; Series II; 33 linear feet
    This series includes materials related to constructing and managing the NPRR's second main rail line. As with Series I, materials in this series exhibit particular attention to the Montana leg of the line; however, they also include records from the Minnesota and Washington state legs. This series is further divided into five subseries--the largest of which details construction projects and traffic reports for the leg between Garrison and Missoula, Montana. Survey records, construction planning correspondence, cost estimates, material requisitions, progress summaries, work force reports, billing records, rights-of-way documents, and design diagrams predominate the series. Construction records detail local and imported supplies as well as work force numbers and pay schedules. Correspondence records provide insights into the challenges engineers faced in designing multiple river crossings due to narrow canyons, procedures and rationales for subcontracting work projects, and long-term operations problems (such as derailments and mud/rock slides).
    Subseries 2, regarding the Garrison to Missoula leg, includes a notable sequence of correspondence, encroachment agreements, and construction designs intended to mitigate the proximity of Northern Pacific Railroad and Milwaukee Railroad lines through narrow stretches of the Clark Fork River valley, particularly near Bearmouth and Clinton, Montana.
    - Bozeman to Logan (Montana) Section, 1910-1913; Subseries 1; 0.5 linear feet
      - Baker and Bear Creek (Montana), Profiles and Locations, 1912 -1913 (Box-folder 38/1)
      - Bozeman to Logan (Montana) Survey, Employment, 1913 (Box-folder 38/2)
      - Bear Creek and Bozeman to Logan (Montana) Lines, 1913 (Box-folder 38/3)
      - Supplies and Equipment, 1913 (Box-folder 38/4)
      - Bozeman to Logan (Montana) Survey, 1910 (Box-folder 38/5)
      - Accounting, undated (Box-folder 38/6)
      - Bridge Supplies, 1912 (Box-folder 38/7)
      - Bozeman to Logan (Montana), Golden Valley-Bear Creek, Time Slips, 1913 (Box-folder 38/8)
    - Garrison to Missoula (Montana) Section, 1906-1910; Subseries 2; 18.5 linear feet
      - American Society of Civil Engineers, 1907-05 - 1909-05 (Box-folder 39/1)
      - Personal Correspondence: F. Beckwith, 1906-12 - 1909-05 (Box-folder 39/2)
      - Bridge Construction, 1906-11 - 1907-06 (Box-folder 39/3)
      - Bridge Construction, 1907-07 - 1908-03 (Box-folder 39/4)
      - Bridge Construction, 1908-04 - 1908-10 (Box-folder 39/5)
      - Bridge Construction, 1908-11 - 1909-01 (Box-folder 39/6)
      - Bridge Construction, 1909-02 (Box-folder 39/7)
      - Bridge Construction, 1909-03 - 1909-09 (Box-folder 39/8)
      - Bulletins, 1907-09 - 1909-04 (Box-folder 40/1)
      - Circular Letters, 1906-12 - 1909-06 (Box-folder 40/2)
      - Cement Expenses, 1908-08 - 1909-05 (Box-folder 40/3)
      - Car Reports, 1906-12 and 1907-05 - 1908-05 (Box-folder 40/4)
      - Car Reports, 1908-06 - 1909-04 and 1909-07 - 1909-08 (Box-folder 40/5)
      - Finishing the Work (report), 1909-09 - 1909-11 (Box-folder 40/6)
      - Construction Payroll, 1910-04 - 1910-06 (Box-folder 40/7)
      - Joint Work Encroachments on Channel Changes and Creeks, 1906-12 - 1907-04 (Box-folder 41/1)
      - Joint Work Encroachments on Channel Changes and Creeks, 1907-05 - 1907-12 (Box-folder 41/2)
      - Joint Work Encroachments on Channel Changes and Creeks, 1908-01 - 1908-12 (Box-folder 41/3)
      - Joint Work Encroachments on Channel Changes and Creeks, 1909-01 - 1909-09 and 1910-01 (Box-folder 41/4)
      - Elevations, 1907-01 - 1907-12 (Box-folder 41/5)
      - Elevations, 1908-01 - 1908-12 (Box-folder 42/1)
      - Damage Claim, Hauswirthe, 1909-03 - 1910-01 (Box-folder 42/2)
      - Flagging, Delays, and Slow Orders, 1907-07 - 1909-05 (Box-folder 42/3)
      - Garrison Depot, 1907-09 - 1908-08 (Box-folder 42/4)
      - Division of Work at Bearmouth, 1909-01 - 1909-02 (Box-folder 42/5)
      - Estimates of Work, 1907-02 - 1909-09 (Box-folder 42/6)
      - Employment Transportation and Passes, 1906-12 - 1907-09 (Box-folder 43/1)
      - Employment Transportation and Passes, 1907-10 - 1908-03 (Box-folder 43/2)
      - Employment Transportation and Passes, 1908-04 - 1908-08 (Box-folder 43/3)
      - Employment Transportation and Passes, 1908-09 - 1909-02 (Box-folder 43/4)
      - Employment Transportation and Passes, 1909-03 - 1909-09 (Box-folder 43/5)
      - Expense Reports, 1906-11 - 1907-05 (Box-folder 44/1)
      - Expense Reports, 1907-06 - 1907-08 (Box-folder 44/2)
      - Expense Reports, 1907-09 - 1907-10 (Box-folder 44/3)
      - Expense Reports, 1907-11 - 1907-12 (Box-folder 44/4)
      - Expense Reports, 1908-01 - 1908-02 (Box-folder 44/5)
      - Expense Reports, 1908-03 - 1908-04 (Box-folder 45/1)
      - Expense Reports, 1908-05 - 1908-06 (Box-folder 45/2)
      - Expense Reports, 1908-07 (Box-folder 45/3)
      - Expense Reports, 1908-08 (Box-folder 45/4)
      - Expense Reports, 1908-09 (Box-folder 45/5)
      - Expense Reports, 1908-10 (Box-folder 45/6)
      - Expense Reports, 1908-11 (Box-folder 46/1)
      - Expense Reports, 1908-12 (Box-folder 46/2)
      - Expense Reports, 1909-01 (Box-folder 46/3)
      - Expense Reports, 1909-02 (Box-folder 46/4)
      - Expense Reports, 1909-03 (Box-folder 46/5)
      - Expense Reports, 1909-04 (Box-folder 46/6)
      - Expense Reports, 1909-05 (Box-folder 47/1)
      - Expense Reports, 1909-06 (Box-folder 47/2)
      - Expense Reports, 1909-07 (Box-folder 47/3)
      - Expense Reports, 1909-08 (Box-folder 47/4)
      - Expense Reports, 1909-09 (Box-folder 47/5)
      - Expense Reports, 1909-10 (Box-folder 48/1)
      - Expense Reports, 1909-12 and 1910-01 - 1910-12 (Box-folder 48/2)
      - Kenyon Forgeries Case, 1907-11 - 1908-04 (Box-folder 48/3)
      - McHugh Irrigation Flume, Willis (Montana), 1907-12 - 1909-03 (Box-folder 48/4)
      - Irrigation Crossings between Drummond and Bonita, Montana, 1906 - 1909 (Box-folder 48/5)
      - Material Requests, 1906-12 - 1907-08 (Box-folder 48/6)
      - Material Requests, 1907-09 - 1908-04 (Box-folder 48/7)
      - Material Requests, 1908-05 - 1909-08 (Box-folder 49/1)
      - Garrison Material Yard, 1906-11 - 1907-12 (Box-folder 49/2)
      - Garrison Material Yard, 1908-01 - 1909-11 (Box-folder 49/3)
      - Payroll, 1906-11 - 1907-10 (Box-folder 49/4)
      - Payroll, 1907-11 - 1908-05 (Box-folder 49/5)
      - Payroll and Timechecks, 1907-09 - 1909-04 (Box-folder 50/1)
      - Payroll and Timechecks, 1909-05 - 1910-01 (Box-folder 50/2)
      - Payroll, 1908-06 - 1909-09 (Box-folder 50/3)
      - Pipe and Culverts, 1907-05 - 1910-01 (Box-folder 50/4)
      - Joint Costs of Pipe and Culverts, 1908-02 - 1908-09 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Personnel, Transfers, Transporation, and Resignations, 1907-04 - 1908-06 (Box-folder 50/6)
      - Personnel, Transfers, Transporation, and Resignations, 1908-07 - 1909-09 (Box-folder 50/7)
      - Personnel, Applications, 1906-10 - 1907-01 (Box-folder 51/1)
      - Personnel, Applications, 1907-02 - 1907-04 (Box-folder 51/2)
      - Personnel, Applications, 1907-05 - 1907-09 (Box-folder 51/3)
      - Personnel, Applications, 1907-10 - 1908-02 (Box-folder 51/4)
      - Personnel, Applications, 1908-03 - 1908-08 (Box-folder 51/5)
      - Personnel, Applications, 1908-09 - 1909-09 (Box-folder 51/6)
      - Rights of Way, Milwaukee Encroachments and Fencing, 1906-11 - 1907-02 (Box-folder 52/1)
      - Rights of Way, Milwaukee Encroachments and Fencing, 1907-03 - 1907-05 (Box-folder 52/2)
      - Rights of Way, Milwaukee Encroachments and Fencing, 1907-06 - 1907-08 (Box-folder 52/3)
      - Rights of Way, Milwaukee Encroachments and Fencing, 1907-09 - 1907-11 (Box-folder 52/4)
      - Rights of Way, Milwaukee Encroachments and Fencing, 1907-12 - 1908-02 (Box-folder 52/5)
      - Rights of Way, Milwaukee Encroachments and Fencing, 1908-03 - 1908-05 (Box-folder 53/1)
      - Rights of Way, Milwaukee Encroachments and Fencing, 1908-06 - 1908-09 (Box-folder 53/2)
      - Rights of Way, Milwaukee Encroachments and Fencing, 1908-10 - 1909-03 (Box-folder 53/3)
      - Rights of Way, Milwaukee Encroachments and Fencing, 1909-04 - 1909-09 (Box-folder 53/4)
      - Construction, Rip Rap, 1908-06 - 1908-11 (Box-folder 53/5)
      - Construction, Rip Rap, 1908-12 - 1909-02 (Box-folder 53/6)
      - Construction, Rip Rap, 1909-03 - 1909-08 (Box-folder 54/1)
      - Steam Shovel Work, 1906-12 and 1907-02 - 1907-09 (Box-folder 54/2)
      - Steam Shovel Work, 1907-10 - 1907-12 (Box-folder 54/3)
      - Steam Shovel Work, 1908-01 - 1908-08 (Box-folder 54/4)
      - Steam Shovel Work, 1908-09 - 1908-10 (Box-folder 54/5)
      - Steam Shovel Work, 1908-11 - 1908-12 (Box-folder 54/6)
      - Steam Shovel Work, 1909-01 and 1909-03 - 1909-05 (Box-folder 55/1)
      - Steam Shovel Work, 1909-06 - 1909-09 (Box-folder 55/2)
      - Materials Requisitions and Cars of Materials, 1906-11 - 1907-03 (Box-folder 55/3)
      - Materials Requisitions and Cars of Materials, 1907-04 - 1907-05 (Box-folder 55/4)
      - Materials Requisitions and Cars of Materials, 1907-06 - 1907-12 (Box-folder 55/5)
      - Materials Requisitions and Cars of Materials, 1908-01 - 1908-08 (Box-folder 56/1)
      - Materials Requisitions and Cars of Materials, 1909-09 - 1909-12 and 1910-05 - 1910-07 (Box-folder 56/2)
      - Track Profiles and Alignment, 1906-12 - 1907-08 (Box-folder 56/3)
      - Track Profiles and Alignment, 1907-09 - 1908-05 (Box-folder 56/4)
      - Track Profiles and Alignment, 1908-06 - 1908-10 (Box-folder 56/5)
      - Track Profiles and Alignment, 1909-05 - 1909-06 and 1910-01 - 1910-12 (Box-folder 56/6)
      - Tunnels, 1906-07 and 1908 (Box-folder 56/7)
      - Tunnels, 1908-08 - 1909-03 (Box-folder 57/1)
      - Work Train Service, 1907-03 - 1907-12 and 1908-04 - 1908-12 (Box-folder 57/2)
      - General Correspondence, 1906-11 - 1907-03 (Box-folder 57/3)
      - Misc, 1907-04 - 1907-05 (Box-folder 57/4)
      - General Correspondence, 1907-06 (Box-folder 57/5)
      - General Correspondence, 1907-07 (Box-folder 57/6)
      - General Correspondence, 1907-08 (Box-folder 58/1)
      - General Correspondence, 1907-09 (Box-folder 58/2)
      - General Correspondence, 1907-10 (Box-folder 58/3)
      - General Correspondence, 1907-11 (Box-folder 58/4)
      - General Correspondence, 1907-12 (Box-folder 58/5)
      - General Correspondence, 1908-01 (Box-folder 59/1)
      - General Correspondence, 1908-02 (Box-folder 59/2)
      - General Correspondence, 1908-03 (Box-folder 59/3)
      - General Correspondence, 1908-04 (Box-folder 59/4)
      - General Correspondence, 1908-05 (Box-folder 59/5)
      - General Correspondence, 1908-06 (Box-folder 60/1)
      - General Correspondence, 1908-07 (Box-folder 60/2)
      - General Correspondence, 1908-08 (Box-folder 60/3)
      - General Correspondence, 1908-09 (Box-folder 60/4)
      - General Correspondence, 1908-10 (Box-folder 61/1)
      - General Correspondence, 1908-11 (Box-folder 61/2)
      - General Correspondence, 1908-12 (Box-folder 61/3)
      - General Correspondence, 1909-01 (Box-folder 61/4)
      - General Correspondence, 1909-02 (Box-folder 62/1)
      - General Correspondence, 1909-03 (Box-folder 62/2)
      - General Correspondence, 1909-04 (Box-folder 62/3)
      - General Correspondence, 1909-05 (Box-folder 62/4)
      - General Correspondence, 1909-06 (Box-folder 62/5)
      - General Correspondence, 1909-07 - 1910-02 (Box-folder 63/1)
      - Estimates of Work, Winston Brothers, 1908-08 - 1908-10 (Box-folder 63/2)
      - Estimates of Work, Winston Brothers, 1908-12 - 1909-03 (Box-folder 63/3)
      - Estimates of Work, Winston Brothers, 1908-07 - 1909-08 (Box-folder 63/4)
      - Expense Reports, 1906-10 - 1908-03 (Box-folder 64/1)
      - Expense Reports, 1908-04 - 1908-09 (Box-folder 64/2)
      - Expense Reports, 1908-10 - 1909-01 (Box-folder 64/3)
      - Expense Reports, 1909-02 - 1909-04 (Box-folder 64/4)
      - Expense Reports, 1909-05 - 1909-08 (Box-folder 65/1)
      - Expense Reports, 1909-09 - 1910-05 (Box-folder 65/2)
      - Boarding and Commissary, 1907-08 - 1907-12 (Box-folder 65/3)
      - Expenses, Subcontractor - Deeks and Deeks, 1907-06 - 1908-12 (Box-folder 65/4)
      - Expenses, Subcontractor - American Bridge Company, Pitts Construction, C.M. Bolton, and Deeks and Deeks, 1908-05 - 1909-06 (Box-folder 65/5)
      - Expenses, Subcontractor - Pitts Construction, 1909-07 - 1909-05 (Box-folder 65/6)
      - Expenses, Subcontractor - Deeks and Deeks, 1909-01 - 1909-07 (Box-folder 66/1)
      - Estimates of Work, 1908-07 - 1909-07 (Box-folder 66/2)
      - Expenses Accompanying Estimates of Work, Robert Brothers, 1907-01 - 1907-02 and 1908-01 - 1908-12 (Box-folder 66/3)
      - Expenses Accompanying Estimates of Work, Robert Brothers, 1909-01 - 1909-04 (Box-folder 66/4)
      - Expenses Accompanying Estimates of Work, Robert Brothers, 1909-05 - 1909-06 (Box-folder 66/5)
      - Expenses Accompanying Estimates of Work, Robert Brothers, 1909-07 - 1909-11 (Box-folder 67/1)
      - Expenses Accompanying Estimates of Work, Winston Brothers, 1907-02 - 1907-12 (Box-folder 67/2)
      - Expenses Accompanying Estimates of Work, Winston Brothers, 1908-01 - 1908-08 (Box-folder 67/3)
      - Expenses Accompanying Estimates of Work, Winston Brothers, 1908-09 - 1908-12 (Box-folder 67/4)
      - Expenses Accompanying Estimates of Work, Winston Brothers, 1909-01 - 1909-09 (Box-folder 67/5)
      - Expenses, Subcontractor - Winston Brothers, 1906-12 - 1908-11 (Box-folder 68/1)
      - Expenses, Subcontractor - Winston Brothers, 1908-12 - 1909-08 (Box-folder 68/2)
      - Expenses, Subcontractor - Rosser and Whitaker, 1907-10 - 1909-01 (Box-folder 68/3)
      - Expenses, Subcontractor - Streeter and Lusk, 1908-01 - 1908-11 (Box-folder 68/4)
      - Expenses, Subcontractor - Robert Brothers, 1908-06 - 1909-12 (Box-folder 68/5)
      - Expenses, Subcontractor - Postal Telegraph Company, Rylander and Company, Brogan and Johnson, Bates and Rodgers, and Palmele and Young, 1907-04 - 1909-03 (Box-folder 68/6)
      - Force Account Reports, 1907-01 - 1907-12 (Box-folder 68/7)
      - Force Account Reports, 1908-01 - 1908-12 (Box-folder 69/1)
      - Force Account Reports, 1909-01 - 1909-06 (Box-folder 69/2)
      - Force Account Reports, 1909-07 - 1909-12 (Box-folder 69/3)
      - Payroll, 1907-01 and 1907-04 - 1907-07 (Box-folder 69/4)
      - Payroll, 1907-08 - 1907-09 (Box-folder 69/5)
      - Payroll, 1907-10 (Box-folder 69/6)
      - Payroll, 1907-11 (Box-folder 69/7)
      - Payroll, 1907-12 (Box-folder 70/1)
      - Payroll, 1908-01 - 1908-04 (Box-folder 70/2)
      - Payroll, 1908-05 - 1908-08 (Box-folder 70/3)
      - Payroll, 1908-09 - 1908-12 (Box-folder 70/4)
      - Payroll, 1909-01 - 1909-05, 1909-10, 1909-12, and 1910-01 (Box-folder 70/5)
      - Return of Time, 1906-12 - 1909-12 (Box-folder 71/1)
      - Work Train Reports, 1907-08 - 1908-04 (Box-folder 71/2)
      - Work Train Reports, 1908-05 (Box-folder 71/3)
      - Work Train Reports, 1908-06 - 1908-08 (Box-folder 71/4)
      - Work Train Reports, 1908-09 - 1908-10 (Box-folder 71/5)
      - Work Train Reports, 1908-11 (Box-folder 71/6)
      - Work Train Reports, 1908-12 (Box-folder 72/1)
      - Work Train Reports, 1909-01 (Box-folder 72/2)
      - Work Train Reports, 1909-02 (Box-folder 72/3)
      - Equipment Failure Reports, 1907-09, 1907-12, and 1908-04 (Box-folder 72/4)
      - Ballast and Grading, 1908-08 - 1909-06 (Box-folder 72/5)
      - Work By Extra Gangs # 7, 1907-11 (Box-folder 72/6)
      - Blueprints of Bridge 103, Erie Division, 1907-10 (Box-folder 72/7)